Welcome to the next
phase, and now it's
time to go one
level deeper in our
pipe system. So you
know that to generate
views and email signups
and sales from YouTube,
all you need to
do is get water
to pass through these
three stages of our
pipe and to warm
it up. But what
I didn't tell you
is that inside each
of these three sections,
there's multiple places that
the pipe gets blocked.
So in this phase,
all we're going to
do is look at
how you can unblock
the very first of
them in the YouTube
section so that water
can actually flow into
your system. So this
phase is about helping
you understand what actually
makes a great YouTube
video. You're going to
learn how to write
titles that make people
want to click. You're
going to discover the
basics of thumbnails, one
of the most important
parts of the system.
We're then going to
go deeper into thumbnails,
the different image strategies
that work. We're going
to look at the
design rules. We're going
to look at how
to use AI to
create thumbnails. And then
after that, we're going
to look at different
types of video formats
that exist and why
this matters a lot,
way more than you
might think when it
comes to getting a
click. And hardly anyone
seems to realize what
I'm going to show
you. So move on
to the next video
where we're going to
move on to the
secret of making content
that brings viewers back
and grows your channel
too. And it's all
about Louis Vuitton.